let quiz = [
    {
        question: "2014 Asia Cup winners?",
        option: [
           "India",
           "Srilanka",
           "Australia",
           "Pakistan",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "2012 T-20 world cup winners?",
        option: [
            "India",
            "England",
            "West Indies",
            "SouthAfrica",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "How many sixes sachin hits in Odi?",
        option: [
            "132",
            "310",
            "195",
            "190",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "How many runs sachin got in his last Odi match?",
        option: [
           "52",
           "72",
           "100",
           "85",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Waca Cricket Ground located in?",
        option: [
            "Loundon",
            "sydney",
            "Durban",
            "perth",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
   
    {
        question: "What is the full form of IPL?",
        option: [
            "Indian Premier League",
            "Intrested Premier League",
            "Indian players League",
            "indonesian Premier League",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What does NBA stand for?",
            option: [
                "National Baseball Association",
                "National Badminton Association",
                "National automobile Association",
                "National Basketball Association",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Who won the first ICC Odi World Cup?",
        option: [
            "India",
            "Australia",
            "England",
            "West indies",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: " Which country will host ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023?",
        option: [
            "Sri lanka",
            "Bangladesh",
            "India",
            "West Indies",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: " Which cricket team has won the 2019-20 Vijay Hazare Trophy?",
        option: [
            "Karnataka",
            "Gujarat",
            "Jharkhand",
            "Tamil Nadu",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: " Which player is given the title of the Flying Sikh?",
        option: [
            "Bahadur Singh Chauha",
            "Milkha Singh",
            "Kamaljeet Sandhu",
            "Harmandeep Singh",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: " india's current cricket caption is?",
        option: [
            "kohli",
            "Rohit",
            "Ms dhoni",
            "Aswin",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the meaning of the phrase umpire calling stumps?",
        option: [
            "The batsman is out",
            "It is a no ball",
            "The play is over for the day",
            "The whole match is over",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "When was the Indian Boxing Federation founded?",
        option: [
            "1970",
            "1965",
            "1949",
            "1979",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who was awarded the “best player” of the 2018 FIFA Football World Cup?",
        option: [
            "Harry Kane",
            "Thibaut Courtois",
            "Kylian Mbappe",
            "Luka Modric",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Ricky Ponting is also known as what?",
        option: [
            "The Rickster",
            "Ponts",
            "Ponter",
            "Punter",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
];
